flairair.ca 2018-09-03

# Flair Air's Privacy Policy - Your privacy protection is important to us.

Except where limited exceptions apply, Flair will always make a reasonable effort to ensure that individuals are notified in advance of the purposes for which their personal information will be collected, used or disclosed and that, where necessary, consent is obtained. Depending on the circumstances, consent may be express or implied.

By using the Website, or by voluntarily submitting information to the Website or Flair Air, you signify your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, you may not use the website, or submit information to Flair Air.

You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions. A decision to withhold or withdraw certain personal information may restrict Flair from offering or providing its services to you.

As standard practice, we will collect personal information from you, and use it and disclose it upon receiving your express consent or from assisting you with booking travel. When you book your travel at [www.flairair.ca](https://flairair.ca/) you are added to our email list that will be used to contact you occasionally with offers By FlairAir Ltd that we feel will be of interest. You can withdraw your consent at any time by scrolling to the bottom of any email offer and click on “unsubscribe” and follow the brief series of instructions.

At times, we may send you service-related emails. These are not promotional emails, rather, they provide important information that must be communicated to you such as flight-related information or updates on purchases made on [www.flairair.ca](https://flairair.ca/).
